<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Hugo's House of Blog Horror - misc</title><link href="https://rfc1437.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://rfc1437.github.io/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://rfc1437.github.io/</id><updated>2020-03-24T13:48:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>SVB Brettspielrunde im Internet</title><link href="https://rfc1437.github.io/svb-brettspielrunde-im-internet.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-03-24T13:48:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T13:48:00+01:00</updated><author><name>hugo</name></author><id>tag:rfc1437.github.io,2020-03-24:/svb-brettspielrunde-im-internet.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hallo und willkommen zur Anleitung für die SVB Brettspielrunde im Internet. Ich versuche hier mal die Schritte zu beschreiben, mit denen ihr in die Runde rein kommt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wichtig zuerst: was braucht ihr? Grundsätzlich einen Computer, vorzugsweise mit Kopfhöhrern und Mikrofon oder Headset. Aber grundsätzlich reicht ein normaler Computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zweite wichtige …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hallo und willkommen zur Anleitung für die SVB Brettspielrunde im Internet. Ich versuche hier mal die Schritte zu beschreiben, mit denen ihr in die Runde rein kommt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wichtig zuerst: was braucht ihr? Grundsätzlich einen Computer, vorzugsweise mit Kopfhöhrern und Mikrofon oder Headset. Aber grundsätzlich reicht ein normaler Computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zweite wichtige Sache: Unten auf der Seite werde ich Bilder von Spielmaterialien verlinken, wenn es welche gibt. Also wenn ihr zu einem Spiel zum Beispiel Spielerhilfen sucht, die sind dann ganz unten!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Installiert haben müsst ihr Google Chrome as Webbrowser. Leider funktioniert das ganze nicht mit Firefox, wenn ihr den benutzt, solltet ihr den Chrome zusätzlich installieren oder habt zusätzliche Schritte durchzuführen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ganz kurz noch ein Hinweis: ihr könnt auf die Bilder klicken, wenn die euch zu klein sind, dann gibt es das Bild in größer und man kann die Texte besser lesen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Computer, Headset / Kopfhöhrer bereit, bequemer Sessel oder Stuhl und auf ins Abenteuer? Wenn ja, kommt als nächstes der Link zur Brettspielrunde:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://teams.microsoft.com/l/meetup-join/19%3ameeting_ZmJlNGE5YTctYzM0NC00ZTcxLWI0Y2QtMmVkYWFiZTIzODdk%40thread.v2/0?context=%7b%22Tid%22%3a%2231f142f5-df76-4112-80a3-19bce6a47b15%22%2c%22Oid%22%3a%22a4c094bc-29b6-459c-b176-8b01655c7038%22%7d"&gt;an SVB Brettspielrunde teilnehmen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wenn ihr auf den oberen Link klickt, bekommt ihr bei Firefox das folgende Bild, das euch sagt, dass ihr Microsoft Teams installieren müsst. Aber ihr habt ja hoffentlich Google Chrome, also ab zum nächsten Bild.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://rfc1437.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/002.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-7801 aligncenter" height="223" src="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/002-300x223.png" width="300"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Das hier folgende Bild kommt bei Chrome. Der wichtige Unterschied: ihr müsst nicht Microsoft Teams installieren (könnt ihr natürlich trotzdem machen, ist aber dann aufwändiger), sondern könnt direkt im Browser teilnehmen. Das ist in der Regel der einfachste Weg. Also in dem Bild dann auf "Stattdessen im Web teilnehmen" klicken. Dann kommt das folgende Bild:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://rfc1437.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/003.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-7802 aligncenter" height="176" src="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/003-300x176.png" width="300"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ihr seht hier, bei mir ist Mikrofon und Kamera aktiv (durch das Kamera Symbol und das Mikrofon Symbol mit dem Schieberegler angezeigt). Eventuell kommt bei euch kurz eine Frage, ob Google Chrome euer Mikrofon und eure Kamera benutzen darf - wenn die Frage kommt, bitte mit Ja bestätigen, damit ihr auch mit den anderen reden könnt. Wenn ihr keine Kamera habt, braucht ihr die Kamera natürlich nicht freigeben. Es gibt keinen Kamera-Zwang, ist nur eventuell auch nett mal wieder die anderen Mitspieler zu sehen. Aber jeder darf auch gerne die Kamera aus lassen, wenn er das nicht möchte.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://rfc1437.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/004.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-7803 aligncenter" height="254" src="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/004-300x254.png" width="300"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was ihr in dem Bild auch seht: da könnt ihr euren Namen eingeben. Vorname reicht völlig, außer ihr wisst, dass noch jemand den gleichen Vornamen hat. Danach dann einfach auf "Jetzt teilnehmen" klicken und ihr kommt nach einer Verbindungspause zu dem folgenden Bild:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://rfc1437.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/005.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-7804 aligncenter" height="185" src="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/005-300x185.png" width="300"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Im Prinzip seid ihr fertig - ich muss euch nur noch in die Brettspielrunde rein lassen. Von daher: wenn ihr das zwischendurch ausprobiert, dann passiert das vermutlich nicht, weil ich nicht ständig in dem Raum bin. Und da es sich um die Server meines Arbeitgebers handelt, bitte einfach in den Abendstunden testen, weil tagsüber hab ich eh keine Zeit mit euch zu testen, da ich arbeite. Abends könnt ihr mich aber gerne per WhatsApp ansprechen, dann lass ich euch in die Besprechung rein und wir können gucken ob bei euch alles klappt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Noch ein kleiner Hinweis: wenn ihr im Raum seid, gibt es einen Steuerungsbalken, mit dem ihr Mikrofon an/aus schalten könnt. Als Bitte: wenn ihr nicht redet, einfach das Mikrofon dort deaktivieren, und nur zum Reden aktivieren, damit nicht alle durcheinander sprechen. Wir kriegen das schon hin. Der Steuerbalken sieht wie folgt aus (und wenn er mal weg ist im Raum, einfach die Maus bewegen, dann taucht er in der Regel wieder auf):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://rfc1437.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/006.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-7809 aligncenter" height="33" src="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/006-300x33.png" width="300"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ihr seht wieder das Symbol für Mikrofon und Kamera, mit denen ihr die beiden Geräte an-/ausschalten könnt. Das Viereck mit dem Pfeil braucht ihr nicht - das benutze nur ich, darüber präsentiere ich das Spiel im ganzen Raum. Die drei Punkte sind für Einstellungen und dann kommt eine Sprechblase, die öffnet oder schließt das Chat-Fenster am rechten Rand. Wenn also mal was klemmt, dann einfach den Chat öffnen und da reinschreiben, das ist oft das einfachste Kontakt zu bekommen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Und damit seid ihr für Donnerstag gewappnet - Spiel aufbauen und online präsentieren übernehme ich, ihr müsst nur reden oder chatten, was ihr in der jeweiligen Spielsituation machen wollt. Ich sorge dafür, das wir Spiele haben, die man auch so spielen kann. Kann sein, dass ich erstmal mit kooperativen Spielen starte, oder mit Spielen, in denen es keine versteckten Informationen gibt - lasst euch einfach überraschen, was kommt. Und - hoffentlich - habt Spaß!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Spielmaterialien&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hier findet ihr Spielmaterialien zum Spiel &lt;a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/EaeNwuLddkqo17876"&gt;Dawn of the Zeds&lt;/a&gt;. Enthalten ist eine Spielerhilfe mit dem Rundenablauf und den Würfeltabellen so wie alle Start-Helden für das Spiel, jeweils mit ihrerer eigenen Story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Für Istanbul ist hier die Spielerhilfe mit Erklärungen der &lt;a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/aUfdsWPSen2NauJX7"&gt;Rundenstruktur und der Bonuskarten&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Für Vinci gibt es hier die &lt;a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/tstF9SgtFmDeDst79"&gt;Regelübersicht und die Kulturfähigkeiten&lt;/a&gt; als Übersicht für jeden Spieler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Für Smallworld gibt es hier die &lt;a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/VkSmZxhPtH8gHiyh6"&gt;Spielerhilfe mit Kulturfähigkeiten und Spezialfähigkeiten&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>Impressum</title><link href="https://rfc1437.github.io/impressum.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2010-11-13T13:39:00+01:00</published><updated>2010-11-13T13:39:00+01:00</updated><author><name>hugo</name></author><id>tag:rfc1437.github.io,2010-11-13:/impressum.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Diese Website ist rein privat betrieben und dient ausschließlich der Darstellung von Ideen und Inhalten des Inhabers. Es besteht kein kommerzielles Interesse. Alle von mir erstellten Inhalte (nicht also z.B. Kommentare, wohl aber meine eigenen Texte und Bilder) sind urheberrechtlich geschützt und &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/2.0/de/deed.de" title="Lizenz für Inhalte"&gt;unterliegen einer Creative Commons Lizenz zur nicht-kommerziellen …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Diese Website ist rein privat betrieben und dient ausschließlich der Darstellung von Ideen und Inhalten des Inhabers. Es besteht kein kommerzielles Interesse. Alle von mir erstellten Inhalte (nicht also z.B. Kommentare, wohl aber meine eigenen Texte und Bilder) sind urheberrechtlich geschützt und &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/2.0/de/deed.de" title="Lizenz für Inhalte"&gt;unterliegen einer Creative Commons Lizenz zur nicht-kommerziellen Nutzung&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inhaber und Verantwortlicher im Sinne des Presserechts ist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Georg Bauer&lt;br&gt;
Am Krug 40&lt;br&gt;
48151 Münster&lt;br&gt;
eMail: &lt;a href="http://hugo.rfc1437.de/kontakt/" title="Kontaktformular"&gt;gb at rfc1437.de&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Telefon: +49 251 4143619&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id="datenschutz"&gt;Daten und deren Protokollierung&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Der Server auf dem meine Webseiten gespeichert sind protokolliert Seitenzugriffe. Da es Github ist, habe ich auf den Umfang der Protokollierung keinen Einfluss. Die Seiten sind aber rein statische Webseiten, es gibt keine dynamische Funktionalität und damit keine durch die Seite selber generierten Benutzerdaten.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>About</title><link href="https://rfc1437.github.io/about.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2010-11-13T10:27:00+01:00</published><updated>2010-11-13T10:27:00+01:00</updated><author><name>hugo</name></author><id>tag:rfc1437.github.io,2010-11-13:/about.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;``&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network Working Group N. Borenstein&lt;br&gt;
Request for Comments: 1437 Bellcore&lt;br&gt;
M. Linimon&lt;br&gt;
Lonesome Dove Computing Services&lt;br&gt;
1 April 1993&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Extension of MIME Content-Types to a New Medium&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Status of this Memo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This memo provides information for the Internet community. It does&lt;br&gt;
not specify an Internet standard. Distribution of this …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;``&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network Working Group N. Borenstein&lt;br&gt;
Request for Comments: 1437 Bellcore&lt;br&gt;
M. Linimon&lt;br&gt;
Lonesome Dove Computing Services&lt;br&gt;
1 April 1993&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Extension of MIME Content-Types to a New Medium&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Status of this Memo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This memo provides information for the Internet community. It does&lt;br&gt;
not specify an Internet standard. Distribution of this memo is&lt;br&gt;
unlimited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A previous document, &lt;a class="externlink" href="http://www.faqs.org/rfcs/rfc1341.html"&gt;RFC 1341&lt;/a&gt;, defines a format and general framework&lt;br&gt;
for the representation of a wide variety of data types in Internet&lt;br&gt;
mail. This document defines one particular type of MIME data, the&lt;br&gt;
matter-transport/sentient-life-form type. The matter-&lt;br&gt;
transport/sentient-life-form MIME type is intended to facilitate the&lt;br&gt;
wider interoperation of electronic mail messages that include entire&lt;br&gt;
sentient life forms, such as human beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other informally proposed subtypes, such as "non-sentient-life-form",&lt;br&gt;
"non-sentient-non-life-form", and the orthogonally necessary but&lt;br&gt;
nevertheless puzzling "sentient-non-life-form", are not described in&lt;br&gt;
this memo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The matter-transport/sentient-life-form MIME type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to promote the wider interoperability of life-bearing email,&lt;br&gt;
this document defines a new MIME content-type, "matter-transport",&lt;br&gt;
and for an initial subtype, "sentient-life-form". This subtype was&lt;br&gt;
designed to meet the following criteria:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. The syntax must be extremely simple to parse, to minimize the&lt;br&gt;
risk of accidental death due to misinterpretation of the standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. The data format must be extremely robust, with redundancy to&lt;br&gt;
ensure that individual life forms will survive and be&lt;br&gt;
reconstituted in such a form as to be nearly indistinguishable&lt;br&gt;
from their initial state, no matter how many bizarre email&lt;br&gt;
gateways are encountered in transit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. The syntax must be extensible to allow for the description of&lt;br&gt;
all yet-undiscovered aspects of life forms which will be required&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for the transport of non-human species (e.g. dolphins, Klingons,&lt;br&gt;
or politicians).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. The syntax must be compatible with SGML, so that with an&lt;br&gt;
appropriate DTD (Document Type Definition -- the standard&lt;br&gt;
mechanism for defining a document type using SGML), a general SGML&lt;br&gt;
parser could be written to parse the data structure and produce&lt;br&gt;
directives to a lifeform-reconstitution mechanism. However,&lt;br&gt;
despite this compatibility, the syntax will most likely be far&lt;br&gt;
simpler than that of full SGML (so that no SGML knowledge is&lt;br&gt;
required in order to implement it), since it is anticipated that&lt;br&gt;
the full complexities of SGML will not be necessary for the&lt;br&gt;
description of even arbitrarily complex organic life forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The syntax of the new content-type is very simple, and indeed makes&lt;br&gt;
considerable sacrifice of efficiency in the interest of simplicity.&lt;br&gt;
It is assumed to describe a three-dimensional rectangular solid, with&lt;br&gt;
the height, width, and depth (calibrated in centimeters) specified as&lt;br&gt;
parameters on the content-type line. (In general, this should be a&lt;br&gt;
cube that completely contains the life form being transported; but,&lt;br&gt;
where high bandwidth is not available, a somewhat smaller cube can be&lt;br&gt;
used, provided that facilities are known to be available at the&lt;br&gt;
recipient's end to administer the medical first aid that could be&lt;br&gt;
necessary if an individual is reconstituted sans some of its&lt;br&gt;
extremities.) A fourth parameter gives the resolution of the matter&lt;br&gt;
scan, calibrated in Angstroms. Thus, the following Content-type&lt;br&gt;
value:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content-type: matter-transport/sentient-life-form;&lt;br&gt;
height = 200; width = 60; depth=60; resolution=10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;implies that the cube being described is 60 cm by 60 cm by 200 cm,&lt;br&gt;
and is described to a resolution of 10 Angstroms. The resolution&lt;br&gt;
gives the quantization unit, and therefore determines the quality of&lt;br&gt;
the reproduction. The data stream itself then consists of a readout&lt;br&gt;
of the molecule found at each location, using the given resolution.&lt;br&gt;
If the resolution is high enough that more than one molecule is found&lt;br&gt;
in a given location, the molecule whose nucleus is closest to the&lt;br&gt;
center of the cube is used. Each molecule is described by its&lt;br&gt;
molecular formula, rendered in ASCII for maximum readability if&lt;br&gt;
matter-transport mail is inadvertently delivered to a human recipient&lt;br&gt;
and displayed on a terminal screen. Each molecule is followed by a&lt;br&gt;
space (ASCII 32) to separate it from the subsequent molecule&lt;br&gt;
description. Extremely long molecules may require the use of a&lt;br&gt;
content-transfer-encoding such as quoted-printable, to ensure that&lt;br&gt;
line-wrapping mail systems do not, for example, cause the unintended&lt;br&gt;
breakdown of complex proteins into their constituent elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is a message that gives a somewhat simplified rendition&lt;br&gt;
of a well-known American politician, starting from the top:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: "Nathaniel S. Borenstein" \&amp;lt;&lt;a href="&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#98;&amp;#64;&amp;#98;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;"&gt;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#98;&amp;#64;&amp;#98;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To: Mark Linimon \&amp;lt;&lt;a href="&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#64;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#115;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;"&gt;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#64;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#115;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Subject: Think hard before reconstructing&lt;br&gt;
Content-description: Dan Quayle, low-res version&lt;br&gt;
Content-type: matter-transport/sentient-life-form&lt;br&gt;
height = 200; width = 60; depth=60; resolution=100000&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 NO2 Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe&lt;br&gt;
Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe Fe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, a real politician's skull is more complex than pure iron,&lt;br&gt;
as is its interior, but this simplified example should give the&lt;br&gt;
general flavor of the protocol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(A caveat, however, in the reconstitution of Vice-Presidents of the&lt;br&gt;
United States: allegedly, some of the matter-reconstitution schemes&lt;br&gt;
currently under development are reputed to perform less than&lt;br&gt;
optimally while trying to reconstitute areas of relatively high&lt;br&gt;
vacuum; for instance, their skulls. A recommended acceptance test&lt;br&gt;
might be to experiment with subjects whose skulls are only at partial&lt;br&gt;
vacuum, such as Vice-Presidents of Marketing.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MHS (X.400) Gateway Considerations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proper behavior of a MIME/MHS gateway with regard to the&lt;br&gt;
transmission of complex multimedia messages is a topic of ongoing&lt;br&gt;
investigation under the auspices of the IETF. The addition of matter&lt;br&gt;
transport should not significantly complicate that effort, as it is&lt;br&gt;
already necessary to specify gateway behavior for MIME types that&lt;br&gt;
have no X.400 equivalents, and matter transport is simply another&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;such untranslatable type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, real-world X.400 gateways might be considered to&lt;br&gt;
significantly increase the hazard that mail containing a human being&lt;br&gt;
will be rejected with a message so cryptic that the recipient deletes&lt;br&gt;
it without ever realizing that an embedded human being is enclosed.&lt;br&gt;
For this reason, it is recommended that the subject of matter&lt;br&gt;
transport be explicitly marked "for further study" in the next&lt;br&gt;
generation of the X.400 specification, X.400-1996. This will give&lt;br&gt;
the community ample time to define a more complete specification for&lt;br&gt;
matter transport as part of X.400-2000, and possibly even a readily-&lt;br&gt;
implementable specification as part of X.400-2004, although some will&lt;br&gt;
no doubt argue that this would be too strong a break with tradition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Implementation Considerations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The user is cautioned against passing MIME transporter messages&lt;br&gt;
through computers equipped with the NFS file system. A no-file space&lt;br&gt;
error caused one of the laboratory rats on our prototype system to be&lt;br&gt;
truncated to a zero-length file. Unfortunately we had neglected to&lt;br&gt;
mount a scratch rat. (We have decided to permanently retain the&lt;br&gt;
empty filename in his honor).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byte swapping problems on other storage systems can be similarly&lt;br&gt;
annoying, but should not be a problem if network byte order is always&lt;br&gt;
maintained ocrrcelty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the authors' belief in the robustness of the protocol,&lt;br&gt;
passage of email through certain systems seems to result in the&lt;br&gt;
sentient-life-form arriving at its destination upside down, resulting&lt;br&gt;
in an annoying "thud". The cause is still under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interoperation with matter-transporters using polar coordinate&lt;br&gt;
systems is discouraged, due to round-off and other algorithmic errors&lt;br&gt;
in certain ubiquitous floating-point implementations, leading to&lt;br&gt;
results which are best discreetly described as "disappointing."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, off-by-one errors should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Widespread adoption of this protocol may lead to an increase in user&lt;br&gt;
demand for reliable backup systems. More importantly, for the first&lt;br&gt;
time management may be motivated to adequately fund such systems when&lt;br&gt;
they discover the possibility that proper email backup may confer&lt;br&gt;
upon them virtual immortality. (On the other hand, implementors&lt;br&gt;
should seriously consider the desirability of making their managers&lt;br&gt;
immortal.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An additional concern reflects the fact that, prior to the&lt;br&gt;
introduction of this content-type, duplicate mail delivery was a&lt;br&gt;
relatively minor nuisance. With the mail extensions described in&lt;br&gt;
this document, however, comes the possibility that duplicate mail&lt;br&gt;
delivery will leave a user with, for example, multiple spouses or&lt;br&gt;
mothers-in-law. The relative weights of the desire to avoid&lt;br&gt;
duplicate delivery and the desire to avoid lost mail may change&lt;br&gt;
accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Security Considerations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Security considerations are not discussed in this memo. However, law&lt;br&gt;
enforcement officials might wish to consider the possibility that&lt;br&gt;
this mechanism could be used by criminals, either to escape&lt;br&gt;
extradition by mailing themselves outside of a legal jurisdiction, or&lt;br&gt;
to outwait the statute of limitations by mailing themselves through&lt;br&gt;
complex mail routes with long delays. (One supposes that they could&lt;br&gt;
also look on the bright side, and consider MIME as a possible&lt;br&gt;
approach to solving the long-standing problem of prison&lt;br&gt;
overcrowding.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors of this document may be reconstituted by feeding the&lt;br&gt;
following data to an Internet-connected MIME reader:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content-type: multipart/mixed; boundary=NextAuthor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--NextAuthor&lt;br&gt;
Content-type: message/external-body; access-type=anon-ftp;&lt;br&gt;
site=thumper.bellcore.com; directory=pub/nsb; name=nsb.flesh&lt;br&gt;
Content-Description: Nathaniel Borenstein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content-type: matter-transport/sentient-life-form&lt;br&gt;
height = 200; width = 60; depth=60; resolution=100000&lt;br&gt;
--NextAuthor&lt;br&gt;
Content-type: message/external-body; access-type=anon-ftp;&lt;br&gt;
site=thumper.bellcore.com; directory=pub/nsb; name=linimon.flesh&lt;br&gt;
Content-Description: Mark Linimon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content-type: matter-transport/sentient-life-form&lt;br&gt;
height = 200; width = 60; depth=60; resolution=100000&lt;br&gt;
--NextAuthor--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authors' Addresses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel Borenstein&lt;br&gt;
Bellcore Room MRE 2D-296&lt;br&gt;
445 South Street&lt;br&gt;
Morristown, NJ 07962-1910&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: (201) 829-4270&lt;br&gt;
EMail: &lt;a href="&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#98;&amp;#64;&amp;#98;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;"&gt;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#98;&amp;#64;&amp;#98;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#46;&amp;#99;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Linimon&lt;br&gt;
Lonesome Dove Computing Services&lt;br&gt;
P.O. Box 20291&lt;br&gt;
Roanoke, VA 24018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone: (703) 776-1004&lt;br&gt;
EMail: &lt;a href="&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#64;&amp;#76;&amp;#79;&amp;#78;&amp;#69;&amp;#83;&amp;#79;&amp;#77;&amp;#69;&amp;#46;&amp;#67;&amp;#79;&amp;#77;"&gt;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#64;&amp;#76;&amp;#79;&amp;#78;&amp;#69;&amp;#83;&amp;#79;&amp;#77;&amp;#69;&amp;#46;&amp;#67;&amp;#79;&amp;#77;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>